# **Envi Bagus Aditya**

### **UI/UX Designer**

Envi is a highly skilled and motivated UI/UX Designer with a passion for digital products. I bring creative design skills and technical expertise to my projects to make intuitive user-centered designs. Have experience working with teams to analyze and create beautiful product design based on requirements and design thinking process using atomic design approach. I am constantly exploring new technologies and design trends, also have some front-end coding experiences.

### **Experience**



#### NATIVE PRODUCTIONS April 2022 - Present

#### Freelance UI/UX Designer

Part-time Pali, Indonesia

- > Designed low-fidelities and high-fidelities for multiple projects in company correlated with Web2 and Web3.
- > Conducted UX research and interview on several projects from start to
- > Coded landing pages website projects using HTML, CSS, Javascript for client projects



#### AIRDROP VENTURES PTE. LTD. September 2022 - January 2023

#### **UI/UX Designer**

Full-time - Semi Remote Singapore

- > Designed and Collaborated with teams in total 3 big projects correlated with Web3 from Low-fidelity into High-fidelity
- > Organised and Built company complex design system for multiple products in Company.
- > UX Researched base requirements and regulation in Indonesia for building products.
- > Directed other UX/UI Designer to maximise workflow in Figma in a tight deadlines utilising Plugins, Shortcuts, Libraries, and Design System.



#### PT. IDOOH BERSAMA INDOESIA June 2022 - October 2022

#### **UI/UX Designer**

- > Designed and Prototyped multiple products following Tailwind UI style
- > Conducted UX Audit some of other products that the company have launch and currently build.
- > Directed 3 UI/UX Designers on teams to maximise the workflow for faster project done.
- > Created complex design system for products and company.
- > Conducted user interview for every new projects, Created user flows, mind map, wireframes, information architecture.



### MERGED, INC. June 2022 - Nov 2022

### Freelance UI/UX Designer

- > Conducted research about most popular payment banking and payment system in the United States.
- > Designed mobile low-fidelity, design system, and high-fidelity of Merged
- > Building prototypes, brand guides to be used for pitching and marketing purposes.



# PT. TIGA TOKEN DIGITAL June 2021 - September 2022

> Created design system for product source of truth

# $\mathbb{N}$ UI/UX Designer

Full-time Pali, Indonesia

- > Designed 6+ big projects related to Web3 including NFT Marketplace, Crypto Wallet Extension, Crypto Exchange, Staking, and Crypto Launchpad as a single UX/UI Designer in company
- > Designed NEFTiPEDiA NFT Marketplace as a main product of company resulted 15,000 Downloaders IOS and Android
- > Coded multiple landing pages for each company website products using HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- > Conducted research about Web3 and Blockchain in designer role.
- > Created graphic design for various events and social media purposes.



# PT. LABELLE PELARIAN INDONESIA Sep - 2019- Nov 2019

# **Product Designer**

Full-time Pali, Indonesia

- > Designed and Managed versioning of Travel agent website app and Community traveling platform that focusing on women using Figma.
- > Conducted UX Research related to the travel agent product
- > Managed website using Docker and Linux.



# VENTRAPEDIA July 2019- Dec 2020

# Freelance Web Designer

Part-time 9 Bali, Indonesia

- > Designed Responsive design of Travel agent website app and Community Platform using Adobe XD.
- > Designed dashboard for managing travel platform. > Coded all the design using HTML, CSS, Javascript with Bootstrap and
- Bulma Frameworks.



#### PT. LUMONATAAug 2017 - Oct 2017 **Web Designer**

# Internship 9 Bali, Indonesia

- > Focused learning Web design and Web development with teams. > Created some graphic designs using Adobe Photoshop and Adobe
- > Participated in multiple website design competitions.
- > Helped some designs and development for the company

### **Contact**



Portfolio Website envibagus.netlify.app



Linkedin linkedin.com/in/envibagus

Phone +62 878 6222 0311

Email envibagus@gmail.com

Location Bali, Indonesia

# Skills

### Design

- › Visual Design
- > Design Thinking
- Mobile Design
- > UX Research
- · Web Design · SAAS Design
- > UX Writing
- > Interaction Design
- > Design System Design Tokens
- > Design Principle
- Figma Libraries
- > Prototyping

#### **Tools**

› Figma

Able to fully maximise features of Figma with plugins, shortcuts, hidden features, and multiple tricks to accelerate workflow for project done.

- > Figjam
- > Zeplin
- > Miro
- > Invision > Maze
- > Framer > Sketch
- > Notion

> Linear

- > ProtoPie
- › Google Workspace
- > Adobe XD
- > Microsoft 365
- > Adobe Illustrator > Adobe Photoshop
- > Atlassian Products

#### **Soft Skills**

- > Problem Solving
- > Project Management
- > Leadership
- > Attention to detail
- > Collaboration > Adaptability
- > Public Speaking

#### Development

> HTML & CSS

> Version Control

- > SQL Database
- > Javascript
- > Bootstrap > Tailwind CSS

- **Certification & Awards** Bootcamp UI/UX & Product Management
- > Design Thinking Techniques for Efficiency

Harisenin.com Bootcamp · January 2023

- Binar Academy · September 2022 > UX Design for Product Development Skill Academy • March 2020
- 3 3rd Winner of Web design Paras ICT 2020 Stiki Indonesia • February 2020
- 2nd Winner of National Group Web design **Techno Art** Universitas Bunda Mulia, Jakarta · April 2019
- 3rd Winner of Web design Paras ICT 2019 Stiki Indonesia • February 2019
- > 1st Winner of Web design PNBWDC Politeknik Negeri Bali • September 2018
- <sup>></sup> 2nd Winner of National Web design Universitas Udayana · June 2018

# **Education**

> Harisenin.com Bootcamp Product Management and UI/UX August 2022 - January 2023

> ITB Stikom Bali

Bachelor Degree in Information System September 2019 - Present

Vocational High school majoring in

Software Engineering July 2016 - July 2019

SMK TI Bali Global

# Languages

- $_{_{>}}$  Indonesian Native or bilingual proficiency
- English
- Professional working proficiency